# **James Lee**

Address: 372 Craig Ave, Staten Island, NY 10307

Email: james.lee84@mail.com

Phone: 330.269.5057

#### **SUMMARY**

Innovative Web Developer with 7+ years of experience in website design, adaptation, and maintenance. Seeking to use extensive knowledge and background in front and back-end web development to advance and optimize the online presence. Possess a Master of Science in Computer Science from UCLA, a Java SE & Programmer Certification, and a CIW User Interface Designer certification.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- **Frameworks**: React.js, Vue.js, Angular.js, Python/Django, Express (Node.js), Ruby on Rails
- CMS: Wordpress, Joomla, Shopify, Squarespace, Wix, Magento
- **Programming languages**: PHP, Java, Ruby, HTML, HTML5, CSS, CSS+, SQL, MySQL, C, C++, C#
- Scripting languages: Javascript, Python
- Graphics Design & UI/UX design
- SEO
- Website troubleshooting
- CRM & ERP platforms

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Lead Developer for Website, iOS & Android projects (Part-time) | RisingIT | AUG 2018~ Present (New York, US)

WEB DEVELOPER | SPINX Digital | SEP 2017~ JUN 2018 (Los Angeles, US)

CTO & Senior Mobile Developer | Small Planet Digital | DEC 2015 ~ JUN 2017 (Los Angeles, US)

Full-Stack Developer | Majestyk Apps | DEC 2010 ~ NOV 2015 (Los Angeles, US)

Android Developer | Heaven and Hell LLC | OCT 2009 ~ DEV 2010 (Los Angeles, US)

## **Previous Works**

Git account

https://github.com/jameslee84

• React.js, Vue.js, Angular.js Works

React.js

https://www.golfdigest.com/

https://www.90min.com/

https://www.agilemd.com/#our-solutions

https://www.buffalowildwings.com/

#### Vue.js

https://www.launchaco.com/

https://www.pathtoproduct.com/

https://www.storyblok.com/

#### Angular.js

https://www.brilliantearth.com/

https://careers.jpmorgan.com/

https://www.ryanair.com/

#### Python/Django Works

https://rankboostup.com/

https://www.semrush.com/

https://inside.com/

https://www.hipmunk.com/

#### • Ruby on Rails Works

https://www.podomatic.com/

https://www.menuism.com/

https://www.crazyegg.com/

## • Express (Node.js) Works

https://depositphotos.com/ https://supplyframe.com/ http://www.surnamedb.com/ https://www.inkedmag.com/ https://stores.soma.com/

#### Wordpress websites built from scratch

https://skillcrush.com/ https://www.tinkeringmonkey.com/ https://www.borngroup.com/ https://www.drinksmart.com/ https://www.protest.eu/ https://www.sparkpost.com/

#### • Joomla Works

https://goldprice.com/ https://www.formilla.com/ https://www.ptotoday.com/ https://fmca.com/

## • Shopify Works

https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/ https://www.happinessabscissa.com/ https://skinny-teatox.com/ https://ratiocoffee.com/ https://www.studioneat.com/

## **Education**

University of California, Los Angeles (2003~207)

Los Angeles Harbor College, Los Angeles (2001~2003)

# **Degrees**

Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Science, University of California Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Computer Science, Los Angeles Habor College

## **Rate & Availability**

- Hourly Rate\$70 per hour
- Hours available per week40 hours per week